<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Code and Loathing</title>
    <link>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Code and Loathing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 12:05:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Automation and Credentials</title>
      <link>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/credentials-for-powershell-scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 12:05:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/credentials-for-powershell-scripts/</guid>
      <description>Credentials in PowerShell PSCredentials objects are widely used in PowerShell by both built-in and 3rd party cmdlets that require credentials as an argument.
To create a PSCredential object interactively we can use the Get-Credential cmdlet.
For example, we could log into Azure AD using the following snippet which will prompt you for the username and password to use.
 $Credential = Get-Credential Connect-AzureAD -Credential $Credential Non-interactive creation of PSCredential But an interactive prompt is not helpful if we want to automate something since the script will just hang waiting for input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype for Business blurry during screenshare</title>
      <link>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/skype-for-business-blurry-during-screenshare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 09:43:56 -0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/skype-for-business-blurry-during-screenshare/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered an issue when screensharing via Skype for Business with some users. The remotely presented screen will be blurry, but if the remote viewer requests control the screenshare will suddenly become clear for them and stay that way even after they release control.
I&amp;rsquo;m guessing there&amp;rsquo;s probably something going wrong with the VbSS (Video based Screen Sharing) mechanism that Microsoft uses now in Skype for Business for screen sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Putty to Serial Port on VirtualBox guest using a Named Pipe</title>
      <link>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/connect-putty-to-serial-port-on-virtualbox-guest-using-a-named-pipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 10:48:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.codeandloathing.com/post/connect-putty-to-serial-port-on-virtualbox-guest-using-a-named-pipe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post describes how to connect to a serial port on a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.virtualbox.org/&#34;&gt;VirtualBox&lt;/a&gt; guest VM using &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/&#34;&gt;PuTTY&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The serial console has traditionally played a special role in system configuration, administration and recovery. Access through this method may provide special elevated privileges and/or not have the same authentication requirements as access through other means.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>